Why are they blocking the path?
Damn it! Cut!
Why did you have to come in now?
Just admit you're obsessed with being in the limelight.
Huh? What's going on?
Didn't you tell him?
Nope, or else he would've gone home.
He isn't interested in such things.
We were trying to capture Hana-poof's reaction!
Too bad.
It's okay.
I'm really happy!
It's the best!
Thank you!
Ji Ah, I thought you went to study.
It's my first time receiving such a surprise.
What? The first time?
I guess you weren't one of the popular kids.
Welcome, Hana-chan.
Clap!
Are those tears? Are you crying?
Finally! More! Cry harder!
Gosh, so pretty!
[Welcome]
What's your favorite Korean food?
Grilled pork belly, spicy rice cakes,
beef tartare, marinated raw crabs...
And... rice in soup, cold noodles, and bingsu (shaved ice)!
- Min Soo?
- Bingsu, you idiot.
What about Korean dramas?
"Myeongdong Class"?
What about movies?
"I'll Do Anything For You".
I'm used to this.
"I'm used to this."
You know what's "rock, paper, scissors," right?
Rock, paper, scissors!
Yahoo!
Alright, rock, paper, scissors!
Nice!
The ultimate loser cleans up!
Rock, paper, scissors!
What are you two doing?
Just clean up together.
Sure!
Ta-da!
Holy hell!
What doesn't she have in that bag?
All done. Let's go.
Come on.
[Episode 2: Blossoming]
[Segi Arts High School]
So pretty.
Pretty, indeed.
Right? So pretty.
Why did you transfer to our school?
I guess, because it has a management course.
So, do you aspire to be a celebrity manager?
Yeah, managers are supposed to be
the closest person to actors in Korea.
I guess so.
My friend aspires to be an actress.
I want to be the closest to her
and someone she needs when her dream comes true.
Wow...
I tagged along with Gu Eun Ho and ended up here.
All good now.
Si Woo, I'll also become someone indispensable to you.
You're my actor, after all!
After that day, the shoelaces she tied
weren't loosened for a long time.
- Yeah...
- Ji Ah, what about your study session?
It was just an excuse to prepare this.
That's good to hear. I thought Ba Reun dragged you here.
Don't worry about it.
Let's go, my princess.
"Let's go, my princess"?
Which kingdom are you from?
She's no princess, but a general!
Hey, look at her glare.
I'm off!
Bye!
Get home safe!
- Bye!
- See you tomorrow.
Oh, right.
Hey, when did you become friends?
Ten years ago.
Okay... And what don't you eat?
I'm too lazy to answer, so stop with the questions.
A manager needs to know everything about their actors.
You aren't supposed to keep secrets from me.
Who told you that?
Ji Ah.
Did she write a textbook or something?
I have no preferences, but Eun Ho can't eat cucumbers.
It's a choice.
Eun Ho can't eat cucumbers.
I said, I choose not to eat it!
Okay, next. Blood type?
What's your guess?
O?
B. Eun Ho's blood type is O.
Are you going to ask about our star signs now?
That was really my next question.
Okay, any allergies?
Neither of us have allergies.
"Us"?
You two sound like a married couple.
What?
You're the closest to each other, share the same dream,
and live under the same roof.
That's just because we grew up together.
Ten years, right?
I'm really envious.
What's there to envy? That guy can't wake up
in the morning even with ten alarms.
Talk about yourself.
Why do you order so much chicken breast meat
when you don't eat them?
I do, when you aren't looking.
Like hell you do. We don't even have space
to store ice-cream now.
You two really are like a married couple.
Okay...
Next...
Look over there!
Hey! Wait up!
Wait for me, Kim Ba Reun!
Ji Ah.
Thank you for being friends with Hana-chan.
You once said you needed a boyfriend, but not friends.
That's because she'll probably be truly happy for me.
I'm always aiming to be the top.
So, I've been sprinting toward that goal.
Other people just pretend to be nice while hoping I trip and fall.
My princess, it's fine to fall.
Don't be so stressed out.
Your dear princess will never trip.
Go on home.
I want to walk you back to your front door.
Not a good day again?
Not a good day at all.
If you bump into my mom...
It'll be such a pain.
Got it.
Off you go.
Bye.
Cheon Si Woo! I'm heading to the laundromat,
want me to bring along your stuff too?
Hang on.
It's cool, just wash your own.
Thanks.
Okay.
Bye.
Who has seen your seniors' uploaded works on social media?
Me!
Make sure you look up the hashtag "SegiArtsHigh".
Understood.
You'll just have to film a reel
and upload it onto your group's account.
I'm sure you've watched many idol survival programs
and their constant appeal tactics.
In the next four weeks,
the group with the most followers and likes...
They'll be the top group, yes?
That's right.
Make sure you upload twice a week and never give up.
Got it?
Why bother when Shin Ji Ah will get first anyway?
We're just here to complement her.
Social media management is a competition.
Brainstorming, planning, filming, and uploading the final work.
It's a chance for our managers to promote their actors.
I want you to create your group accounts within this week.
Ji Ah, can I speak with you for a moment?
Sure.
[Management, Shin Ji Ah, Payment Status]
This is about the workshop fee...
My mother must've forgotten.
Alright, let her know then.
I will.
[Consultation Room]
Mom, I told you about...
Mom, you'll get your salary in the next two days, right?
Ji Ah, I'm really envious that you have no troubles.
Brainstorming, planning, filming, uploading...
What in the world is all this?
I'm better off taking a plane back to Japan.
Just do it. What's there to worry about?
But I'll be bothering Eun Ho and Si Woo.
Even a selfie from them would get tons of likes.
That's true, they're wonderful.
But I really want to make their charms shine brighter.
I'm hardly on social media.
All the photos I upload are of cats.
In that case, start by studying how to film and edit videos.
Was that a hint?
Off I go!
[2025 Short Video Editing and Marketing...]
[Starting a film production project]
Film production...
Social media...
Alright.
[Short Videos]
Eun Ho's a cat.
Si Woo's a puppy.
You're the Japanese manager for our Eun Ho?
I'm the leader of the Heartbroken Gu Eun Ho Girls, a.k.a H.G.G.
These two just like a handsome face.
My dream is to be Eun Ho's girlfriend.
All the best!
There's always been a tradition with Eun Ho's managers.
- Tradition?
- Provide H.G.G with photos of Eun Ho in casual clothes.
Please!
Why?
We're always starving for more since there are so little rations.
Why not ask him for it?
Eun Ho isn't interested in girls!
He's devoted to acting.
You've snatched the privilege to be around Eun Ho all the time.
Should I transfer to the management course?
Anyway, the other managers always did so.
It's your turn now.
Don't tell Eun Ho about this or you're...
dead.
Let's go.
Where's Si Woo?
Not here yet.
Too handsome?
Yup... Yup, yup.
So...
Eun Ho, can you take a selfie?
Why should I?
I want to brag to my friend.
Who is this friend of yours?
A friend...
in Japan?
No.
Just one.
Can't you help me out here?
You guys can start first.
Eek, it's Gu Eun Ho!
Eun Ho? But I look like crap now!
Wait. Don't come near.
I told you to stay back!
You couldn't even say a word to Shin Ji Ah.
I guess you were waiting for a new manager to appear.
The first year managers always did so,
and now it's your turn.
Don't tell Eun Ho about this or you're...
dead.
Hey.
Like hell the second year managers would take those photos.
Don't expect me to do anything.
And you're wasting my time.
Get out of my way.
Watch it!
Ma'am, I bumped into crazy fans of Gu Eun Ho
from the acting course.
This is a violation of school rules, right?
Get moving.
Happy now?
Is Hana an errand girl to you?
This is my final warning.
Don't ever talk to my managers.
I'll... make sure Shin Ji Ah is swapped back.
So handsome!
Hey.
Stop squealing when you see me, got it?
Yes, sir.
I guess his manager's called Hana.
Gu Eun Ho! Do you even know my name?
Damn it! This is the first time you've come to me, you know?
Why make it the last?
Give me another warning! Anything!
You're so freaking handsome!
Super!
He's so handsome!
Look, I'm also in the background.
One, two, three.
Okay, let's do it.
One, two, three!
One more!
Rabbit!
So cute.
Where were you? We waited for ages.
Waited? You're clearly having fun.
Hana-chan, should we start the meeting?
Yeah.
We have to film reels, don't we?
Apparently, the first three seconds determine everything.
When there are more comments and likes,
the algorithm pushes the video to more people...
What is it? A challenge video? A meme?
Yes, memes!
What do you watch? I like funny videos.
By the way, I don't do funny content.
I didn't say a word about that.
You two just have to look good.
That's my only idea.
It's your only weapon.
What should we do?
The issue is coming up with a concept.
Let's head out.
Why?
To have fun!
Come on!
Move it.
Be careful. Watch your step.
Ta-da!
This place is nice, right?
What's this?
[life4cuts]
- Eun Ho.
- Hurry up.
Go on in.
Amazing!
Come closer.
One, two, three.
It's blue!
- Over there?
- Yeah.
So pretty!
- Very pretty.
- Right?
Let's take a look.
Look what I've got!
And in it goes.
Clack!
It's really pretty.
[Hana, Si Woo]
This place is gorgeous!
Si Woo, try saying something.
I'm filming a test video.
Ta-da! I'm in Namsan right now!
I'm hungry.
Let's grab something to eat.
Eun Ho.
What?
What do you want to eat?
Is this your first time here?
We have to eat pork cutlets at Namsan.
Let's go! Pork cutlet time!
Bingo.
Si Woo, look over here.
Be careful. It's dangerous.
I'll be fine.
Are you okay?
- I'm okay.
- I told you to be careful.
Give me the phone.
I'm confiscating it.
- Be careful.
- The kind Si Woo.
Watch your step.
- Got it.
- Be careful.
Enjoy your food.
Stop filming.
Turn the camera off.
Jeez.
Do you like it when your food is cold?
The aloof Eun Ho.
[Namsan Pork Cutlets]
Did I get that right?
Let's talk about our concept.
How about an exchange student's video log
of male Korean friends?
Having fun and eating good food just like today.
So, you think having fun and editing some videos will cut it?
- Don't be rude.
- That's not what I mean.
I never appear in the videos.
- And so?
- Here's what I think.
It'll help viewers feel like they're right with you.
Like having a date with two handsome friends.
Hana-chan, you're a genius.
I like it. Let's go with it.
I guess we can try uploading something.
I think it's worth a shot...
We should try it.
Kind male friend.
Aloof male friend.
Wow, what a total girlfriend perspective.
What, is he my boyfriend?
This is amazing.
- They're cute.
- Gu Eun Ho's so cute!
He's so handsome.
Like it first.
Hey, have you seen this?
- Like!
- Don't you think he's really good-looking?
I like the guy who looks like a puppy.
I like the cat-looking one.
I guess they're trending these days.
How can someone be so handsome?
Gu Eun Ho?
So handsome.
He's totally like my boyfriend!
No, he's my boyfriend!
Our Eun Ho's cutting pork cutlets?
This is insane!
Our Eun Ho is out of this world!
Hey! You guys!
Look at this! The likes are through the roof!
Thailand, Indonesia, even America!
Folks from all over the world are liking our videos!
Great job, Hana-chan.